[Music] Let's
[Música]
see, let's take a look at the
A ver vamos a echar un vistazo a lo de
hland thing, yesterday with Leo we couldn't
los hland que ayer con to Leo no pudimos
get it on yesterday with all of Leo the truth is
echárselo ayer con tod Leo la verdad es
that this year the thing is it's
que este año el tema es
turning out a little fail, I came in
la está saliendo fail un poco fail venía
as more professional and they came in as more
como más profesional y venían como más
eager with more desire but it's turning out
ganas con más ganas pero está saliendo
a little so-so let's go commenting
un poco regulín vamos a ir comentando
okay let's go commenting on everything a little
vale vamos a ir comentando todo un poco
here and
aquí y
kime anything please anything we
kime cualquier cosa porfa cualquier cosa
're talking about to Add
de la que estemos hablando para Añadir
if you send it to me I appreciate it okay
si me lo mandáis os lo agradezco vale en
first of all
primer lugar se respeta la decisión de
the streamers' decision is respected For example auron
los streamers Como por ejemplo auron
Play Javi was more badass man but not
Play Javi era más cañero hombre pero no
more badass more badass more charismatic funnier
más cañero más cañero más carismático
more likable and I was doing a thousand
más gracioso más simpático y me iba mil
times better because you can't
veces mejor porque es que no puedes
compare he wants to be a jail from 2018 and
comparar él quiere ser un jail de 2018 y
come on and but above all when you
vamos y pero sobre todo cuando tienes
already have experience to learn from dude
experiencia ya de la que aprender tío
Because I came in, he's super duper you know
Porque yo venía va super burro sabes
but when you have experience dude to
pero cuando tienes experiencia tío de la
learn from thing that really there won't
que aprender movida que que realmente no
be any problem because Well
va a haber ningún problema porque Bueno
then we have agreed with
pues nos hemos puesto de acuerdo con con
these people from  the people
estas personas de las de las personas
who openly expressed their
que expresaron abiertamente su
disagreement with being in the eslan there
disconformidad de estar en los eslan no
is no one who is nominated who does not
hay nadie que esté nominado que no lo
want to be Exactly except
quiera estar Exacto exo menos a día de
today This is worth it or rather the people who do not
hoy Esto que vale o sea la gente que no
want to go are not going to be there by force Javi
quiere ir no va a estar por [__] Javi
opened the mailman totally the people
le abría el cartero totalmente la gente
who do not want to be there are not going to be there by
que no quiere estar no va a estar por
force like when gref said Well then I'm
huevos como cuando dijo gref Bueno pues
going to nominate you because yes it's not worth it these
te voy a nominar porque sí no vale estos
are the anger of the year anger of the year
son los enfado del año enfado del año
okay for the nominees Agustín 51 this
vale por los nominados Agustín 51 esto
is a photo it's a photo I don't know what
es una foto es una foto no sé qué click
specific click it's a photo it sounds familiar to me from
en concreto es es una foto me suena por
the game The one who is playing that we have
el juego Al que está jugando que lo
seen it could have put the click damn they could have put the
hemos visto podían Haber puesto el click
click DJ
[__] podían Haber puesto el click Dj
Mario but Jer they could have put the
Mario pero Jer podían Haber puesto el
click the one with Messi It was a joke it was not
click el de Messi Era una broma no era
anger it's nonsense the one with Messi does not even
un enfado es una tontería el de Messi ni
know he has 3000 clips to put
saste tiene 3000 clips para ponerle
tacker metal Ricky edit Ricky Ed
tacker metal Ricky edit Ricky Ed
nominated for anger of the year the River I
inominado por enfado del año la River Yo
have some this and I do not see this
es que hay alguno esto y esto no lo veo
anger of the year  But well the one from Cesar
enfado del año Pero bueno el de César
bluey is very good this one from wcol I don't know
bluey es muy bueno este de wcol no sé
what anger it is but come on there are some that I
qué enfado es pero vamos hay algunos que
see a little there are some that I see a
lo veo un poco hay algunos que lo veo un
little bit of finger putting in for putting in okay
poco a dedo meter por meter vale
streamer irl okay with this one there was a little
streamer irl vale con este hubo un
problem because of the issue of the because of the
problemilla por el tema de la por el
hours Okay now I'll explain
tema de las horas Vale ahora os explico
alana arro and misfortune I don't know who is who is who is
alana arro y desgracia no sé quién es
and he has me blocked
quién es quién es y me tiene bloqueado
who the [ __ ] is this I have no [ __ ]
quién [__] es esto no tengo ni putísima
idea who is who is this super
idea de quién es quién es este super
Random brunenger Green japan Jordi kidy
Random brunenger Green japan Jordi kidy
juna living on the street Mario and Mario
juna viviendo en la calle Mario y Mario
t the typical ones are nominated the
t los típicos sea están nominados los
main ones I would say is a friend of gref he's from
principales yo diría es amigo de gref es
Javi's kitchen here a controversy that I
de cocina Javi aquí una polémica que
think is up here the deen I
creo que está aquí arriba lo
understand that if bellingham if
deen entiendo que si bellingham si
bellingham scores 150 goals in 30 games
bellingham mete 150 goles en 30 partidos
and mbappe scores 30 goals in 150 games
y mbappé mete 30 goles en 150 partidos
the Ballon d'Or you're going to give it to
el Balón de Oro se lo vas a dar a a
mbappe I have stayed 5 and a half hours to
mbappé Me he quedado a 5 horas y media a
a Stream okay this is what he said first
un Stream vale esto que ha dicho primero
of Los Balones
de Los Balones
e La  The thing is that of course the issue of the
e La Movida es que claro el tema de la
average number of viewers how the hell do
media de espectadores cómo [__] calculas
you calculate who has been the most relevant because of
tú Quién ha sido más relevante porque
course if you put it by h if you put it by
claro si lo pones por h si lo pones por
hours viewed
horas vista puede ganar perfectamente
a person who doesn't have as many
una persona que tenga no tantos
viewers as others but is on
espectadores como otros pero que esté
for many hours can perfectly win, okay? But if you put it
muchísimas horas vale Pero si lo pones
by average it's also a problem because
por media también es un problema porque
if you put it by average It's like for
si lo pones por media Es como por
example in the news I put The
ejemplo en el noticiero he puesto yo El
example of telesalseo telesalseo has
ejemplo de telesalseo telesalseo ha
had some amazing programs but
tenido unos programon que flipas pero
amazing the whole Daniel Sancho issue
que flipas todo el tema de Daniel Sancho
has taken the cake telesalseo but with the
se la ha llevado telesalseo pero con los
programs that I've done alone with the
programas que he hecho yo solo con los
programs that I've done with trium, I mean
programas que he hecho con trium o sea
with trium there wasn't a night that didn't have
con trium no había noche que no tuviera
between 8 and 13,000 viewers every
entre 8 y 13,000 espectadores todas las
night with the Daniel Sancho issue
noches con el tema de Daniel Sancho
other programs too two or three I did
otros programas también dos o tres hice
with Fran Cuesta with more than 20,000
con Fran cuesta con más de 20 25,000
viewers
espectadores
and the Álvaro Prieto issue also an
y el tema de Álvaro [__] también una
outrage
barbaridad
eh the programs with Marina or rather in the
eh los programas con Marina o sea en el
heart issue eh Teres salseo And mik
tema del corazón eh teres salseo Y mik
Vasco because M Vasco  every night it
Vasco porque M Vasco todas las noches
has between 6 and 8000 viewers,
tiene entre 6 y 8000 espectadores
even nine are fixed, but of course if
incluso nueve vale fijos pero claro si
I also start doing live shows in
yo me pongo a hacer también directos por
the afternoon, there's another day that I do it. eh. In
la tarde hay otro día que lo hago eh Por
the morning there have been many live shows that I've
la mañana ha habido muchos directos que
done in the morning. eh. In the
lo he hecho por por la mañana eh Por la
morning with 1000 viewers, at noon
mañana con 1000 espectadores al mediodía
with 2000, of course, the average goes down, of course. So
con 2000 claro la media baja claro
what do you do? You only
Entonces qué es lo que hace solamente
do the good live shows, the ones that
haces los directos los buenos los que
you're going to have more or less high so that
vas a tener más o menos alta para que no
the average doesn't go down. No, I have to
te vajes la media No yo tengo que
work hard, I have to inform, there are mornings
trabajada tengo que informar hay mañanas
that suddenly it was good for me to open
que de repente me venía bien abrir
live. When I've been traveling, many
directo cuando he estado de viaje muchas
times I've done live shows in the center of
veces he hecho directo por el centro de
Porto, in Vigo, it's also a live show. No, of
Porto en vigo también es un directo No
course.
claro
Eh. Did you see the video of Gato Purron? No, I didn't
Eh Viste el vídeo de gato ronron no no
know. César. I didn't know that he had made a
sabía César no sabía que había hecho un
video. Remind me now then that's
vídeo recordármelo ahora entonces eso es
very such Mik Vasco. We made the
muy tal mik Vasco nosotros hicimos la la
table. Well, of course, it didn't add up to me. eh.
tabla Pues claro no me cuadraba a mí eh
Many things about
No me cuadraban a mí muchas cosas de
these nominations didn't add up to me, and the fact that Mik wasn't
estas nominaciones y que mik no
there, if he was guided by the
estuviera si estaba guiado por el
clear M in the average, he surpasses several of
claro m en la media supera a varios de
those who are  nominees in
los que están nominados en cobertura
news coverage okay it surpasses several but
informativa vale supera a varios pero
very easily okay telesalseo I think
muy tranquilamente vale telesalseo creo
exactly no eh telesalseo
que justamente no eh telesalseo
exactly did not surpass anyone of those who are
justamente no superaba a nadie de los
nominated I think eh in averages there is
que está nominado creo eh en medias hay
another channel that is gossip chisme like
otro canal que es de chisme chisme like
or something like that it is called that it is a
o algo así que se llama que es un canal
gossip channel that has every night 14
de chisme que tiene todas las noches 14
15000 20000 viewers okay they have not
15000 20000 espectadores vale es no han
counted on it I do not know why okay of course
contado con él no sé por qué vale claro
what is happening that it does not pass the
qué es lo que pasa que no pasa el
criteria of 300 hours by very little
criterio de las 300 horas por muy poco
we are talking about
estamos hablando de
239 live I mean almost every day
239 directos O sea casi todos los días
Eh of 50 minutes 200 hours it is missing 100 hours of
Eh de 50 minutos 200 horas le faltan 100
course chisme no like it is missing 100
horas claro chisme no like le faltan 100
hours Jamaica of course 300 is a
horas Jamaica claro es que 300 es una
[ __ ] outrage 300 a bit outrageous
[__] barbaridad 300 un poco barbaridad
then of course How do you do it so that it is
entonces claro Cómo lo haces tú para
good because the issue of the
para que esté bien porque el tema de la
average then the issue of the I think
media tal luego el tema de las Yo creo
brendy a kiss I think that the issue
que brendy un beso Yo creo que el tema
of the hours even  It may be on
de las horas incluso puede que sea a
purpose to leave people out. I mean,
propósito para dejar fuera gente O sea
Mike does a live stream almost every day,
Mike hace directo casi todos los días
we're talking about 200 or so
estamos hablando de 200 y picos de
live streams, what does he want? The thing is that
directos qué quiere lo que pasa es que
they're 50 minutes long because that's how she does it,
son de 50 minutos porque ella lo hace
she prepares her monologue and so on. You
así ella se prepara su monólogo y pin
know, I've been 5 and a half hours away from
Sabes Me he quedado a 5 horas y media a
a Stream. I've been one Stream away from being
un Stream Me he quedado a un Stream de
categorized as a streamer, I mean,
que se me categorice como streamer o sea
I cared more about the irl than the
me importaba más el irl que la
revelation. The revelation doesn't matter to me, I don't care,
revelación la revelación me pela me la
but I've worked hard on each Stream like
pela pero me he currado cada Stream como
the most, like the most, what I
el que más como el que más lo que yo
do is very difficult, it's very difficult. I
hago es muy [__] es muy [__]
understand that. Besides, I'm going to
entiendo que además Aparte te voy a
tell you something else, well, it wouldn't matter
decir otra cosa bueno no importaría
because the average would go down. Not that on TV,
porque bajaría la media No que en tv to
if you have less than, I don't know how many
si tienes menos de no sé cuántos
viewers, less than 1000, they don't
espectadores menos de 1000 no
count. Shas wanted to put 5600 hours,
cuentan el shas quería poner 5600 horas
man, no. I see that 200 was fine
hombre no Yo veo que 200 estaba bien
for me, he should win this award x Cry,
para mí debe ganar este premio x Cry la
honestly. I mean, I think that the concept of a
verdad O sea creo que el concepto de
revelation streamer as such. I mean, it can't be, I
streamer revelación como tal O sea no lo
mean, he's the perfect example of
puede es decir es el ejemplo perfecto de
what a good streamer is, the
lo que es un streamer bueno la categoría
revelation category has  it's been a nonsense
de revelación ha sido un despropósito
neda What are you saying, in fact, Nilo heda
neda Qué dices tú per si Nilo heda hace
10 years ago was already the [ __ ] boss I mean, what
10 años ya era el [__] amo O sea qué me
are you
estás
telling me? Who was Nilo heda espurcito
contando Quién era Nilo heda espurcito
exp purito is in revelation purito was already
exp purito está en revelación purito ya
breaking it when I met him in 201 16
lo petaba cuando yo lo conocí en 201 16
and Cry was already breaking it a while ago it's
y Cry ya lo petaba hace tiempo s que es
true that what's happening now
verdad que no tiene sentido lo de ahora
with the shipping but but Cry has already had
con el shipeo pero pero Cry ya ha tenido
many good stages too eh
muchas etapas también buenas eh
revelation whether you like it more or less
revelación te guste más o te guste menos
is what it is, revelation streamer as
es lo que es streamer revelación como
such a concept from the numbers you
tal concepto de desde los números que
have to how far you get in a short
tienes hasta dónde llegas en un corto
period of months is that it is the
plazo de meses es que es el ejemplo
absolutely perfect example I would
absolutamente perfecto yo me quedaría
also maybe stay with dbo it
también quizá con dbo
was Crystal mly dude it was Crystal Molly
era Crystal mly tío era Crystal Molly
Crystal mly has managed to gain
Crystal mly ha llegado este año a ganar
more than half a million followers on
más de medio millón de seguidores en
Twitch this year dude it was Crystal mly these Which
Twitch tío era Crystal mly estos Cuáles
are the most Innova streamers of the year Well El
son streamers del año má Innova bueno El
Rubius has also come out In the end El
Rubius ha salido también Al final El
Rubius has also come out today in the end the
Rubius ha salido hoy también al final lo
Cry thing he put it in because since it is so
de Cry la metido porque como está tan de
fashionable now, so strong the shipping thing Javi
moda ahora tan fuerte lo del shipeo Javi
reacts to  responding to that V I think I have it
reacciona a respondiendo a ese V creo
now we'll see You're
que lo tengo ahora lo vemos Me estáis
sending me a lot of homework and it's 2:30
mandando muchos deberes y son las 2:30
eh I don't know how far we're going to go well It
eh No sé hasta dónde vamos llegar bueno
depends on how I treated you with the likes and
Depende cómo os porté con los likes y
with the members It depends on how I treated you
con los miembros Depende cómo os porté
with the likes and with the members okay
con los likes y con los miembros vale
crystal mooli don't have the hours it's not
cristal mooli no ten las horas tampoco
done much Stream too no dude eh
se hace mucho Stream también no tío eh
gref I wanted to put it in for balls but because I'm lazy it's
gref quería meter por huevos pero por
not worth it I say it sincerely and not to
huevín no va lo digo sinceramente y no
make myself humble let them give the
por hacermelo humilde que le den el
award to other people I've been eating a lot for 10 years it's the
premio a otra gente Yo ya llevo 10 años
rest of the people's turn It's
comiendo mucho le toca al resto de gente
going to be more excited if it's a
le va a hacer más ilusión que le toque a
new streamer or one who's been here for a short
un streamer nuevo o que lleva poco
time or one who's been here less time than me
tiempo o que lleva menos tiempo que yo
give everything to the rest of the people Don't say
que le den todo al resto gente No digas
[ __ ] it's not [ __ ] I've had
[__] no son [__] he tenido
enough in my life I don't need
suficiente en mi vida no me hace falta
anything else I know that someone is going to appreciate it
nada más sé que alguien lo vo a apreciar
more than me I'm telling you that a guy with I don't
más que yo te digo yo que a un tío de yo
know
que sé
50,000 followers or something like that is going to
50.000 seguidores o algo así le va a
be a billion times more excited
hacer mil millones de veces más ilusión
and I want that person to have that excitement
y quiero que esa ilusión la tenga esa
you know
persona sabes
but then it's that it's  that doesn't make
ya pero es que entonces es que es que no
sense Then it doesn't make much
tiene sentido Entonces no tiene mucho
sense eh It doesn't make much sense let's see
sentido eh No tiene mucho sentido a ver
the one that has grown the most has been River with
el que más ha crecido ha sido River con
3 million Followers and goes with 3
3 millones de Seguidores y va con 3
million Mariana but it's not about, I mean,
millones Mariana pero es que no se trata
Cay has grown a lot I hope that we
de o sea cay ha crecido mucho Ojalá
are this not any of
nosotros que siamos esto no cualquier
these years that suits us but of
año de estos que nos venga bien pero
course it's from where you come to, I mean,
claro es de donde tú vengas a o sea
revelation it's from where you come to
revelación es de donde tú vengas hasta
where you get that year, I mean Who would be
donde llegues ese año o sea Quién sería
revelation this year
revelación este año
Who would be revelation this
Quién sería revelación este
year, revelation man Who would be
año revelación tío Quién sería
revelation uncle Roger I don't know what
revelación tío Roger es que no sé lo que
Roger does I don't follow the promo they
hace Roger no lo sigo la promo que le
give to deg all the people All
dan a deg toda la gente Todos
reacting to the nominations us
reacionando las nominaciones nosotros
here too Well it's good content
aquí también Bueno es un buen contenido
Who would be a revelation man Cay Javi
Quién sería una revelación tío cay Javi
Cry but I Cry doesn't see it as a revelation
Cry pero yo Cry no lo ve revelación
because many times there's no
porque muchas veces es que no hay por
way to take it, it hasn't exploded in viewers
donde cogerlo no ha petado en viewers
that going from 2k to 5k is not a revelation
que pasar de 2k a 5k no es revelación
that he has gained many followers on
que haya ganado muchos seguidores en
Twitter and other platforms and on Twitch they
Twitter y otras plataformas y en Twitch
don't see you grazing well Of course because
no te ven a pastar bueno Claro porque
only the Stream is taken into account of course
solo se tiene en cuenta el Stream claro
I look at it  like something in general
Yo es que lo miro como algo en general
I've seen Cry on many occasions he's
yo a Cry lo he visto en muchas ocasiones
had calmer times and
que ha tenido épocas más tranquilita y
stronger times but Cry has had
épocas más fuerte pero Cry ha tenido
times where you've said wow the
épocas que has dicho tú [__] vaya los
numbers that the guy has
numerazo que tiene el tío
eh what was missing in the anger of the year the
eh faltó dentro del enfado del año el
Ricky clip my truth our truth
clip de Ricky mi verdad nuestra verdad
we should do something man I'm going to
nosotros deberíamos hacer algo tío voy a
talk to delox eh so he can be my
hablar con el delox eh para que sea mi
my producer and we can do some
mi productor y hagamos un unas
nominations for the gossip man I mean
nominaciones del salseo tío o sea
literally we nominate Ricky edy For that
literalmente nominamos a Ricky edy Por
teaser we nominated for anger of the year
ese teaser nominamos al enfado del año
they are categories that hit in our in
son categorías que pegan en nuestro en
our Awards The thing is that I don't
nuestros Premio Lo que pasa es que no
have anyone to produce me and I and
tengo a nadie que me produzca y me y me
put me and put me the money to put on
ponga y me ponga la pasta para ponerme
the event I'm going to talk to delon my
el evento voy a hablar con delon mi
millionaire friend or with rups so that so
amigo millonario o con rups para que
that they finance us and and we do it
para que nos financie y y lo hagamos
because this is that this doesn't seem to me this no
porque esto es que esto no me parece
this hasn't turned out very
esto no esto no ha quedado muy en
well the
condiciones la
[Music]
[Música]
truth
verdad